>> 扬声器 1: 除了基本值外，我们还具有基本对象。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: In addition to our primitive
values, we also have fundamental objects.
顺便说下这是我最近介绍的术语
And by the way, this is a terminology that
I think was somewhat recently introduced
在此规范中。
in this spec.
这些都被称为内置物体
And these used to be referred
to as built-in objects or
甚至是土生土生
maybe even native functions.
我曾提到这些历史上的自然函数。
I've referred to these
historically as native functions.
我认为它们现在更常被称为基本物体。
I think they're more commonly now
referred to as fundamental objects.
那么，以你的任何一个短语来说，选择和选择。
So whichever phrase works for
you, pick and choose.
但如果你读这个规范
But if you're reading this spec, and
你会看到像一个基本物体的东西这就是它的来源
you see something like a fundamental
object, that's where this comes from.
那么这些基本的物体是什么，它们是类型吗 ?
So what are these fundamental objects,
are they types?
有点像但不太好
Sort of, but not really.
这就好比是基于 JavaScript 的对象的定位，
This is like the kind of bolted on
object orientedness of JavaScript,
几乎是 Java 型的 JavaScript 变种
the almost Java-like
mutation of JavaScript
在那些我们有原始价值的案例中
where we have in all of those cases
where we have primitive values,
我们现在还具有类似行为的对象表示。
we now also have object representations
with similar behaviors.
比如当你想做字符串的时候
Like in Java when you
want to make a string and
你称它为新的资本 S 弦我们有类似的情况
you call it new capital S string,
we have things like that in JavaScript.
我不认为你应该用它们，但我认为你应该理解它们。
I don't think you should use them, but
I do think you should understand them.
所以这些是你真正应该用这个新关键词的地方，
So these are the ones where you really
should absolutely use the new keyword,
对象，数组，函数，日期，正则表达式，错误。
Object, Array, Function, Date,
Regular Expression, Error.
如果您需要构造该基本类型的对象，
If you need to construct an object
of that fundamental type,
然后使用新对象，新阵列或新函数。
then use new Object, or
new Array, or new Function.
例如，我将会使用的钥匙可能是新日期。
Probably the key one here that I would
use would be new Date, for example.
但还有一些基本的物体是可以用的
But there are other ones that are
fundamental objects which could be used
全新的但我要告诉你肯定不能用新的
with new, but I'm gonna tell you you
should definitely not use them with new,
即这三个，字符串，数字和布尔值。
and that is these three,
string, number, and Boolean.
它们可用于构造此表单的对象。
They can be used with new to
construct the objects of this form.
你绝对不应该这样做
You should absolutely never do that.
您应该仅将它们用作函数而不是构造函数。
You should use them only as functions,
not as constructors.
当我们在胁迫的时候谈论
And when we talk about
later in coercion and
你就会明白他们的用处
you'll understand the usefulness of them.
但是字符串，数字和
But String, Number, and
当用作函数时，布尔会将任何值强制转换为相应的基本类型。
Boolean when used as a function coerce any
value to that respective primitive type.
那是一个更有用的实用程序
That is a far more useful utility of those
比他们能建造这个奇怪的科学怪人物的事实
than the fact that they can construct
this weird Frankensteiny object.
所以在这里再举一个例子，我说新的日期
So an example here again Date,
I would say new Date
以构造日期对象，因为没有日期文字。
to construct the date object why
because there is no date literal.
如果要进行日期，那么必须执行新日期。
If you want to make dates,
you have got to do new Date.
这也许是我认为我们应该保持新经营者的唯一原因
That might be the only reason why I think
we should keep the new operator around
因为我需要从时间到时间，这是唯一的办法。
because I need to make dates from time to
time and that is the only way to do it.
我希望有一天他们会加入一个日期的文字
I do hope that maybe someday
they add a date literal.
但是，我们还没有做到这一点。
But, we don't have that yet.
所以我可以建造日期但如果我有一些不是绳子的东西
So I can construct dates, but if I have
something that is not already a string,
例如，如果我的 JSON 对象背面有 myGPA 的 myGPA ，那么
for example, if I got a JSON object
back that had myGPA from college in it,
我在这里告诉你大学的 mgGPA 是什么
here I am telling you what
myGPA in college was.
如果我回了个 JSON 对象，那是我大学的成绩单
If I got back a JSON object,
that was my transcript from college and
它有我的 mysGPA 但是我得把它作为一个字符串
it had myGPA in it, but
I needed to represent it as a string,
大写 S 字符串函数执行此操作并正常运行。
capital S string function does that and
does it well.
它将其转换为该字符串表示。
It converts it to that
string representation.